{\rtf1\ansi\ansicpg1252\cocoartf1404\cocoasubrtf470
{\fonttbl\f0\froman\fcharset0 Times-Roman;\f1\fmodern\fcharset0 Courier;}
{\colortbl;\red255\green255\blue255;\red0\green0\blue0;}
\margl1440\margr1440\vieww10800\viewh8400\viewkind0
\deftab720
\pard\pardeftab720\sl280\partightenfactor0

\f0\fs24 \cf2 \expnd0\expndtw0\kerning0
\outl0\strokewidth0 \strokec2 This XML file does not appear to have any style information associated with it. The document tree is shown below.\
\pard\pardeftab720\sl300\partightenfactor0

\f1\fs26 \cf2 <!--\
    RSS generated by SHRM v1.25.3980.218  on 7/7/2016 10:48:04 AM\
-->\
<rss version="2.0">\
<channel>\
<title>GlobalHR</title>\
<link>\
https://stg-kafka-www.shrm.org/rss?listname=rss%26itemtitle=globalhr\
</link>\
<ttl>60</ttl>\
<category>Global and Cultural Effectiveness</category>\
<category>Global HR</category>\
<item>\
<title>\
<![CDATA[ Diverse Thinking Encourages Innovation ]]>\
</title>\
<link>\
https://stg-kafka-www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/behavioral-competencies/global-and-cultural-effectiveness/pages/diverse-thinking-encourages-innovation.aspx\
</link>\
<description>\
<![CDATA[\
In the business world, where innovation is desired, \'93assumptions can be very dangerous. People don\'92t know what we don\'92t know,\'94 said Ann Herrmann-Nehdi, chief executive officer of Herrmann International in Lake Lure, N.C.\
]]>\
</description>\
<category>Diversity and Inclusion</category>\
<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>\
</item>\
<item>\
<title>\
<![CDATA[\
First Time Dealing with Immigration? Seek Legal Help\
]]>\
</title>\
<link>\
https://stg-kafka-www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/talent-acquisition/pages/first-time-immigration-seek-legal-help.aspx\
</link>\
<description>\
<![CDATA[\
HR practitioners new to immigration matters must first understand the two main types of visas\'97employment and business-based\'97and the processes involved in securing both.\
]]>\
</description>\
<category>Global Business Outsourcing</category>\
<category>Immigration and Visas</category>\
<category>Global and Cultural Effectiveness</category>\
<category>Global HR</category>\
<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>\
</item>\
<item>\
<title>\
<![CDATA[ H-1B Woes? Consider the TN Visa, Experts Say ]]>\
</title>\
<link>\
https://stg-kafka-www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/talent-acquisition/pages/h-1b-consider-tn-visa.aspx\
</link>\
<description>\
<![CDATA[\
The TN visa category is a useful tool when recruiting skilled professionals\'97especially when the H-1B visa option dries up\'97provided the individuals are citizens of Canada or Mexico.\
]]>\
</description>\
<category>Immigration and Visas</category>\
<category>Global and Cultural Effectiveness</category>\
<category>Global HR</category>\
<category>Global Talent Acquisition</category>\
<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>\
</item>\
<item>\
<title>\
<![CDATA[ Attract Top Talent with Personalized Rewards ]]>\
</title>\
<link>\
https://stg-kafka-www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/talent-acquisition/pages/attract-top-talent-personalized-rewards.aspx\
</link>\
<description>\
<![CDATA[\
Think globally and act locally when designing total rewards to attract great talent, said consultant and thought leader John Rubino during a concurrent session June 22 at the Society for Human Resource Management 2016 Annual Conference & Exposition in Washington, D.C.\
]]>\
</description>\
<category>External Recruiting</category>\
<category>Benefits--Global</category>\
<category>Global and Cultural Effectiveness</category>\
<category>Benefits</category>\
<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>\
</item>\
<item>\
<title>\
<![CDATA[ Affirmative Action Isn\'92t Dead ]]>\
</title>\
<link>\
https://stg-kafka-www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/legal-and-compliance/employment-law/pages/affirmative-action-university-of-texas.aspx\
</link>\
<description>\
<![CDATA[\
Concerns that the Supreme Court would find the use of affirmative action in higher education to be unconstitutional were put to rest, as the court upheld the University of Texas' admissions factors, which included consideration of race in limited circumstances.\
]]>\
</description>\
<category>Diversity and Inclusion Compliance</category>\
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>\
</item>\
<item>\
<title>\
<![CDATA[ Intel HR: Make Sex Transition a Partnership ]]>\
</title>\
<link>\
https://stg-kafka-www.shrm.org/hr-today/news/hr-news/pages/intel-hr-make-sex-transition-a-partnership.aspx\
</link>\
<description>\
<![CDATA[\
2016 Annual Conference &amp; Exposition Conference Today - Keep up to date on all #SHRM16 news and updates. Newsletter - Sign up for the free HR Daily newsletter to receive Conference Today. Photos \'b7 Conference InformationAn employee\'92s transition from one sex to another is a process that can take years and that can affect the employee\'92s co-workers. To ensure that there is as little disruption in the workplace as possible and to help the transitioning worker, HR should partner with the employee in terms of strategy, support and communications, recommended Eva Breslin, SHRM-SCP, an HR legal representative with Intel Corp. in Rio Rancho, N.M.At Intel, there is a single point of contact for an employee who is transitioning to help him or her through the many changes that must take place at work, she remarked during a concurrent session June 21 at the Society for Human Resource Management 2016 Annual Conference &amp; Exposition.Typically, the first step is the employee communicating wit\
]]>\
</description>\
<category>Gender Identity</category>\
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>\
</item>\
<item>\
<title>\
<![CDATA[\
Developing a Global Mindset Is Critical to Organizational Success\
]]>\
</title>\
<link>\
https://stg-kafka-www.shrm.org/hr-today/news/hr-news/pages/developing-a-global-mindset-is-critical-to-organizational-success.aspx\
</link>\
<description>\
<![CDATA[\
2016 Annual Conference &amp; Exposition Conference Today - Keep up to date on all #SHRM16 news and updates. Newsletter - Sign up for the free HR Daily newsletter to receive Conference Today. Photos \'b7 Conference InformationAs more organizations conduct business outside the countries where they are headquartered, it is becoming necessary for employees of those companies to develop a global mindset as they work with people in other parts of the world.\'93We don\'92t see things as they are, we see things as we are,\'94 said Dean Foster, quoting from Ana\'efs Nin\'92s 1958 novel Seduction of the Minotaur. Foster, president of New York City-based DFA Intercultural, conducts cross-cultural training worldwide and consults on intercultural business issues with Fortune 500 companies in the U.S. and around the world.He spoke June 20 at the Society for Human Resource Management 2016 Annual Conference &amp; Exposition.Someone from Brazil, for example, might characterize people in the U.S. as cautious and meth\
]]>\
</description>\
<category>Other Global HR Topics</category>\
<category>Global and Cultural Effectiveness</category>\
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>\
</item>\
<item>\
<title>\
<![CDATA[ Could a 6-Hour Day Work for Full-Time Employees? ]]>\
</title>\
<link>\
https://stg-kafka-www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/global-hr/pages/could-a-6-hour-day-work-for-full-time-employees.aspx\
</link>\
<description>\
<![CDATA[\
Work for six hours but be paid for eight? Some businesses in Europe are experimenting with the idea. In February 2015, 80 assistant nurses at an elder care home in Gothenburg, Sweden, began working a 30-hour week made up of six-hour workdays on an eight-hour salary as part of a controlled trial. They are being compared to the same number of staff members working a traditional eight-hour day at a similar employer, according to a BBC report. The New York Times reported that an audit published in mid-April of the six-hour schedule \'93concluded that the program in its first year had sharply reduced absenteeism, and improved productivity and worker health.\'94A hospital in Gothenburg also moved to a six-hour workday, along with two hospital departments at a facility in Umea, also in Sweden. At a Toyota service center in Gothenburg, mechanics have worked six-hour shifts for eight hours\'92 worth of pay since 2002. And Agent Marketing in Liverpool, England, conducted a trial six-hour workday in Decem\
]]>\
</description>\
<category>Other Global HR Topics</category>\
<category>Global and Cultural Effectiveness</category>\
<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>\
</item>\
<item>\
<title>\
<![CDATA[\
Reducing New Employee Turnover Among Emerging Adults\
]]>\
</title>\
<link>\
https://stg-kafka-www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/employee-relations/pages/reducing-new-employee-turnover-among-emerging-adults.aspx\
</link>\
<description>\
<![CDATA[\
If a job isn\'92t meaningful to them, emerging adults aren\'92t afraid to leave--quickly.\
]]>\
</description>\
<category>Other Employee Relations Topics</category>\
<category>Employee Engagement</category>\
<category>Other Diversity Topics</category>\
<category>Generations</category>\
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>\
</item>\
<item>\
<title>\
<![CDATA[ In Focus: A Look at Overtime Laws Around the Globe ]]>\
</title>\
<link>\
https://stg-kafka-www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/global-hr/pages/in-focus-a-look-at-overtime-laws-around-the-globe.aspx\
</link>\
<description>\
<![CDATA[\
The United States is not alone in reassessing the workweek and payment of overtime. Sweden is experimenting with a 6-hour workday, while the state government of Maharashtra has enacted an amendment that allows all workers to put in more overtime. Here are more news updates about overtime around the world&#58;&#160; United Kingdom&#58; Employers 'Will Cut Overtime and Weekend Pay' to Meet Living Wage A report by Manpower shows workers may see little difference in pay packets after firms make savings in other areas. (The Guardian) Is French 35-Hour Work Week Under Siege? The 35-hour maximum work week in France soon&#160;could come to an end. Plans from French&#160;President Fran\'e7ois Hollande would whittle away at the rigidity of the&#160;35-hour work week and make it easier for employers to fire their workers, the Economist&#160;reported. (International Business Times)India&#58; State Amends Factories Act to Allow More Working Days and Overtime The state government of Mahara\
]]>\
</description>\
<category>Other Global HR Topics</category>\
<category>Global and Cultural Effectiveness</category>\
<pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>\
</item>\
<item>\
<title>\
<![CDATA[\
Self-Regulation Can Prevent Government Intervention\
]]>\
</title>\
<link>\
https://stg-kafka-www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/global-hr/pages/self-regulation-can-prevent-government-intervention.aspx\
</link>\
<description>\
<![CDATA[\
It hasn\'92t taken Australia\'92s assistant federal treasurer Kelly O\'92Dwyer long to hit the ground running in the year following the country\'92s latest Financial Systems Inquiry, which aimed to establish a direction for the future of Australia\'92s financial system.&#160;In the wake of the inquiry findings, O\'92Dwyer, one of Prime Minister Malcolm Turnbull\'92s new ministers, has left no doubt in anyone\'92s mind that the government expects financial planning advisers to substantially lift their game. She recently announced that they will be required by law to hold a degree, to undertake a professional year, to pass an exam, to commit to continuous professional development (CPD) and to subscribe to a code of ethics.&#160;One might wonder what previous standards financial advisers were required to satisfy if these fairly general qualifications must now be mandated under legislation. Aren\'92t all professional practitioners required to meet standards as fundamental as these?The dismaying fact is that financia\
]]>\
</description>\
<category>Australia</category>\
<category>Global and Cultural Effectiveness</category>\
<pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>\
</item>\
<item>\
<title>\
<![CDATA[\
EEOC Panel Looks at Promoting Diversity, Inclusion in High-Tech\
]]>\
</title>\
<link>\
https://stg-kafka-www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/behavioral-competencies/global-and-cultural-effectiveness/pages/eeoc-panel-looks-at-promoting-diversity-inclusion-in-high-tech.aspx\
</link>\
<description>\
<![CDATA[\
Women, workers over age 40 and other protected groups face significant challenges if they want to work in the technology industry, according to panelists speaking during a U.S. Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC) public meeting.\
]]>\
</description>\
<category>Gender</category>\
<category>Race</category>\
<category>Age</category>\
<category>Diversity and Inclusion Initiatives</category>\
<pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>\
</item>\
<item>\
<title>\
<![CDATA[ View from Thailand: AEC Opens Labor Markets ]]>\
</title>\
<link>\
https://stg-kafka-www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/global-hr/pages/view-from-thailand-aec-opens-labor-markets.aspx\
</link>\
<description>\
<![CDATA[\
In Thailand, we are already seeing the effects following the December 31, 2015, kickoff of the ASEAN Economic Community (AEC) in which the 10 countries that make up the Association of Southeast Asian Nations (ASEAN) are coming together with the huge purchasing power of up to 660 million people.The vision for the AEC is a single market with a free flow of goods, capital and skilled labor, which should make the region more attractive for foreign investment. However, this is a region characterized by the charm of differences between each member state in terms of social, economic and political development level and institutional capability. There is a lot of playing field to level.The Thai government is working hard to communicate the implications of the AEC to all Thais through a variety of channels, including television, radio, electronic media and newspaper. The majority of the government\'92s communication effort is targeted especially at small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs), which m\
]]>\
</description>\
<category>Global and Cultural Effectiveness</category>\
<category>Asia</category>\
<pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>\
</item>\
<item>\
<title>\
<![CDATA[\
EEOC Report: High-Tech Firms Hire Fewer Minorities Compared to All Industries Nationwide\
]]>\
</title>\
<link>\
https://stg-kafka-www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/behavioral-competencies/global-and-cultural-effectiveness/pages/eeoc-report-high-tech-firms-hire-fewer-minorities-compared-to-other-industries-nationwide.aspx\
</link>\
<description>\
<![CDATA[\
Employment in computer science and engineering is growing at twice the rate of the national employment average overall, yet there are \'93significantly\'94 fewer female, black and Hispanic employees in those jobs, which often provide higher pay and better benefits, according to a new report. \'93The distribution of workers among job groups in the high-tech industry nationwide suggests a pattern where women and nonwhite employment decreases as the job group increases, from technicians up to executives,\'94 said Ronald Edwards, director of the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC) Program Research and Surveys Division. The EEOC released the report May 18 during a public hearing and panel discussion.Black employees, for example, make up 9 percent of high-tech technicians but only 1.9 percent of executives, Edwards noted.The Diversity in High Tech report looked at national and Silicon Valley data from the Employer Information Reports (EEO-1s) collected in 2014. The report defined high-tech in\
]]>\
</description>\
<category>Gender</category>\
<category>Race</category>\
<category>Color</category>\
<pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>\
</item>\
<item>\
<title>\
<![CDATA[\
EEOC Report: High-Tech Firms Hire Fewer Minority Workers Than All Industries Nationwide\
]]>\
</title>\
<link>\
https://stg-kafka-www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/behavioral-competencies/global-and-cultural-effectiveness/pages/eeoc-report-high-tech-firms-hire-fewer-minority-workers-compared-to-all-industries-nationwide.aspx\
</link>\
<description>\
<![CDATA[\
Employment in computer science and engineering is growing at twice the rate of the national employment average overall, yet there are \'93significantly\'94 fewer female, black and Hispanic employees in those jobs, which often provide higher pay and better benefits, according to a new report. &#160;\'93The distribution of workers among job groups in the high-tech industry nationwide suggests a pattern where women and nonwhite employment decreases as the job group increases, from technicians up to executives,\'94 said Ronald Edwards, director of the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC) Program Research and Surveys Division. The EEOC released the report May 18 during a public hearing and panel discussion.Black employees, for example, make up 9 percent of high-tech technicians but only 1.9 percent of executives, Edwards noted.The Diversity in High Tech report looked at national and Silicon Valley data from the Employer Information Reports (EEO-1s) collected in 2014. The report defined high-t\
]]>\
</description>\
<category>Gender</category>\
<category>Race</category>\
<category>Color</category>\
<pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>\
</item>\
<item>\
<title>\
<![CDATA[\
Transforming HR in Asia-Pacific: We Have a Choice to Make\
]]>\
</title>\
<link>\
https://stg-kafka-www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/global-hr/pages/transforming-hr-inasia-pacific.aspx\
</link>\
<description>\
<![CDATA[\
The transformation of human resources as a practice and a profession has been an important issue in the past. It has become critical now.The evolution has been taking place over several years, and we have made progress in reducing costs, utilizing resources effectively, outsourcing some human resource activities, and improving operations and partnerships, among other things. But overall, HR has yet to take on a full leadership role in achieving business objectives through its strategies.&#160;The practice of HR in the Asia Pacific region is still generally lagging behind that in the West. In some places, such as Australia and Singapore, and within a few specific organizations in other countries, HR operations have adopted the more mature global practices of Europe and North America, but many other countries and organizations still use an outdated \'93personnel management\'94 approach. The Asia Pacific region represents the largest population in the world while also supplying skilled and unsk\
]]>\
</description>\
<category>Global and Cultural Effectiveness</category>\
<category>Asia</category>\
<pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>\
</item>\
<item>\
<title>\
<![CDATA[ DOL Overtime Rule Will Challenge Recruiting ]]>\
</title>\
<link>\
https://stg-kafka-www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/talent-acquisition/pages/dol-overtime-rule-challenge-recruiting.aspx\
</link>\
<description>\
<![CDATA[\
New regulations governing overtime pay will have a significant impact on recruitment, employers say, from scaling back hiring to rebranding roles that have been downgraded from salaried to hourly.\
]]>\
</description>\
<category>Overtime Eligibility and Exemptions</category>\
<category>Overtime Pay</category>\
<category>Global and Cultural Effectiveness</category>\
<category>Global HR</category>\
<category>Global Talent Acquisition</category>\
<pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>\
</item>\
<item>\
<title>\
<![CDATA[\
Employee Recognition Should Consider Personal, Generational Preferences\
]]>\
</title>\
<link>\
https://stg-kafka-www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/behavioral-competencies/global-and-cultural-effectiveness/pages/personal-touch-generational-preferences-recognition-program.aspx\
</link>\
<description>\
<![CDATA[\
Acknowledging employees\'92 work and behavior is an important retention strategy, but organizations need to keep in mind generational preferences and the importance of the personal touch.\
]]>\
</description>\
<category>Generations</category>\
<category>Rewards and Recognition</category>\
<pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>\
</item>\
<item>\
<title>\
<![CDATA[ When Should Pay Go Global? ]]>\
</title>\
<link>\
https://stg-kafka-www.shrm.org/resourcesandtools/hr-topics/compensation/pages/pay-goes-global.aspx\
</link>\
<description>\
<![CDATA[\
Should multinational companies manage employee compensation as a global whole, allow local compensation practices to predominate, or perhaps take a hybrid approach?\
]]>\
</description>\
<category>Compensation</category>\
<category>Compensation--Global</category>\
<category>Global and Cultural Effectiveness</category>\
<pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>\
</item>\
<item>\
<title>\
<![CDATA[\
Changing Destructive Behavior to Become a Conscious Leader\
]]>\
</title>\
<link>\
https://stg-kafka-www.shrm.org/hr-today/news/hr-magazine/pages/changing-destructive-behavior-to-become-a-conscious-leader.aspx\
</link>\
<description>\
<![CDATA[\
In her new book, Conscious Leadership in the Workplace&#58; A Guidebook to Making a Difference One Person at a Time (Morgan James Publishing, 2016), executive coach Rosalie Chamberlain&#160;reveals that self-awareness\'97the framework for how we see ourselves\'97also influences how we see others. It is the starting place to determine how effectively you lead. Are you biased? How diverse is your team? Do you embrace inclusion?\'93Successful organizations foster an environment of inclusion, and this behavior promotes engagement and motivation which, in turn, drives innovation,\'94&#160; Chamberlain says. \'93Conscious leadership guides individuals and leaders to realize their potential, breaking through beliefs and behaviors that impede success.\'94 Chamberlain, @rosaliechamberl on Twitter, is a certified coach and leadership practitioner who works with organizations and individuals to identify behaviors that motivate, inspire and create, as well as those that block creativity and performance.&#\
]]>\
</description>\
<category>Other Diversity Topics</category>\
<pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>\
</item>\
</channel>\
</rss>\
}